{
    "subject": "Rodney_Dangerfield",
    "predicate": "produced",
    "object": "Rover_Dangerfield",
    "human_readable": "Rodney Dangerfield produced Rover Dangerfield.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8801882863044739,
            "question": "Who produced the film Rover Dangerfield?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8584024310112,
            "question": "Who is Rover Dangerfield?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.837337851524353,
            "question": "What is the name of the film produced by Rodney Dangerfield?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8289636969566345,
            "question": "Is Rodney Dangerfield known for producing films?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8040903210639954,
            "question": "Who played the role of Rover Dangerfield?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7766215801239014,
            "question": "Can you name any other films produced by Rodney Dangerfield?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7161706686019897,
            "question": "What type of work is associated with Rodney Dangerfield?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6821831464767456,
            "question": "What was Rodney Dangerfield's career primarily focused on?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6026184558868408,
            "question": "Is Rover Dangerfield a fictional character?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.45246759057044983,
            "question": "What genre is the film Rover Dangerfield likely to belong to?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Rodney Dangerfield produced Rover Dangerfield.",
            "html": "yago_22786_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is Rover Dangerfield a fictional character?",
            "html": "yago_22786_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What was Rodney Dangerfield's career primarily focused on?",
            "html": "yago_22786_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What type of work is associated with Rodney Dangerfield?",
            "html": "yago_22786_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_22786_35.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_22786_49.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_22786_53.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_22786_55.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_22786_6.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_22786_73.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_22786_74.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_22786_80.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_22786_83.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_22786_94.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the answer in the form of a structured JSON format:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents indicate that Rover Dangerfield is a 1991 American animated musical comedy film, and multiple files mention that Rodney Dangerfield wrote and co-produced the film. Therefore, it can be inferred that Rodney Dangerfield produced Rover Dangerfield."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents mention that Rodney Dangerfield wrote and co-produced the film \"Rover Dangerfield,\" which supports the statement that Rodney Dangerfield produced the said film."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {'output': 'yes'}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": "is true",
            "full_ans": "0.9"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": "is true",
            "full_ans": "0.9"
        }
    },
    "final_decision": "true",
    "actual_decision": "true",
    "analysis": {
        "error_category": "caafscd",
        "error_detail": "cdscsd",
        "category": "csdcs",
        "stratum": "fwefew",
        "topic": "wefw"
    }
}